Robson Burns

robson.burns@yahoo.co.uk	07701 384797
--------------------------	--------------

Profile

Throughout my education and employment, I have demonstrated high levels of motivation, work ethics, this has been demonstrated by my continued dedication and excellent attendance and my ability to finish tasks to competition, I have also achieved the highest grades in my BTEC extended diploma. I pride myself on arriving early to my university classes, and I consider to be reliable, punctual and hardworking, this can be seen throughout all my assignments.

Work Experience

Baker Blower Precision Engineering	Stanley St, Sheffield
CNC Machinist - Trainee	10/10/2018 - 21/09/2019
This was a part time role of 22 hours per week whilst I completed my BTEC qualification at Sheffield College. The role entailed machine operating, part set up, general workshop activities, coding, etching & part assembly.	
OSL Cutting Technologies	Burgess Rd, Sheffield
Assembling Tools	22/02/18 - 19/04/18
	(Only Thursdays)
This was a voluntary work experience placement as part of my BTEC qualification. The role included magnetic bench drilling, soldering and wiring.	
Andrew Tovey Jewellers	Newton Lane, Sheffield
Workshop Assistant	18/7/16 - 22/7/16
This was a voluntary work experience placement at secondary school. This was a Jewellers workshop where I assisted in soldering, sorting of gems.	

Education

Sheffield Hallam University	Sheffield
BSC HON Computer Science	Sept 19 to present
Modules: Algorithms and Data Structures,	
Fundamentals of Computer Architecture,	
Fundamentals of Programming for Computer	
Science, Maths for Computer Science,	
Professional Experience and Project	
Development, Systems Modelling.	

Sheffield College	Olive Grove, Sheffield
	Sept 2017 - Jun 2019

BTEC Level 3 Extended Diploma in Engineering (D*D*D*)	
Meadowhead School Academy Trust	Meadowhead, Sheffield
10 GCSEs A-C: Mathematics Higher (6),	Sept 2012 - Jun 2017
English Language (4), Computer Science (B),	
Core Science (B)	

Technical Skills

In my time in university I have been able to become exceptionally familiar with various programming languages and programmes, some of which are:

- C++
- CSS
- Python
- ADL
- HTML

As well as these languages I have also used:

- Visual studio
- Visual studio code

Skills

- I can work in a team and take instructions well but can easily work independently.
- I have acquired good management skills as part of my most recent role.
- I am also ways punctual and am prepared for the tasks ahead.

Interests

I enjoy my time at home on my computer as I am an avid gamer, as well as this I enjoy socialising with my friends, this would include visits to the cinema and other activities.

References

John London	Baker Blower Precision
Production Manager	Stanley St
johnlondon0611@gmail.com	Sheffield
07867532524	S3 8HH

Martin Cooper	Sheffield Hallam University
Tutor/Mentor	Arundel gate
m.j.cooper@shu.ac.uk	Sheffield
01142256984	S1 2NU

Any of my References are available upon request.